http://www.harlow-college.ac.uk/get-in-touch/terms-conditions

HomeWelcomeLoginSmart SearchStudy OptionsHNC & HNDA LevelsT LevelsVocational CoursesApprenticeshipsHigher EducationAccess to HEPart-time & Adult CoursesEnglish, Maths & ESOLBright FuturesSupported StudiesOnline and On Campuse-LearningLeadership and ManagementStansted Airport CollegeEmployersHAMECChoose UsCareers AdviceHere to HelpBe an AmbassadorStudent LifeWe Win AwardsMake a DifferenceFor EmployersApplyOnline Applicant HubEnrolment FAQsFull-time CoursesPart-time CoursesApprenticeshipse-Learning CoursesLearner LoansCountdown to CollegeYour CommitmentOpen EventsFull-time Guide 2021/22Stansted Airport College Guide 21-22Study Levels ExplainedAboutReturn to College FAQsTerm Dates 2020/21COVID-19 AdviceNews & EventsGovernanceJob VacanciesUpcoming EventsSafeguardingPoliciesEquality & DiversitySixth FormSkylight RestaurantHAMECTravel InfoDigital SupportData ProtectionFinancialsApple Distinguished SchoolBritish Values at Harlow CollegeNew Student InfoContactFind UsCourse EnquiriesHow Are We Doing?Terms & ConditionsStay in TouchSupport Services
Careers start here.
Take control of your future!
HomeContact
Website Terms & Conditions
Your personal information is safe with us
We'll add your details to our mailing list and every email you get from us will have the option to unsubscribe. We'll send you details of course offers and events and we may also use it for statistical analysis.
Our commitment to your privacy
Harlow College is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our site and the confidentiality of the personal information with which you provide us.
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
Harlow College is registered under the General Data Protection Regulation and we comply with the Act in all our dealings with your personal data.
The information you provide will be held by Harlow College and used in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation. Your inf­ormation will not be passed to third parties.
How we will use your data
We will use it to contact you with details of course offers and events. We may also use the information for statistical analysis.
When you send an enquiry to the college using one of our Contact Us forms we will add your email address to our mailing list. All emails you receive from us will offer the option to unsubscribe from our list.
When users of our site send us personal information, such as their email address, The College undertakes:
Never to sell your details to anyone
Never to give your details to any third party without your express agreement
To only use the information in order to shape and improve the services we offer.
All data is collected anonymously unless explicitly stated otherwise.
Any information collected indirectly will be only be used by Harlow College to:
monitor the volume, type and pattern of traffic using this website
develop the design and layout of the website and for other administrative and planning purposes.
About our website
This website contains information about the services and courses offered by Harlow College.
Every effort has been made to ensure the accuracy of the information contained on this website but Harlow College cannot accept any responsibility for errors or omissions, or for any consequences arising from the use of information contained herein.
The College reserves the right to introduce changes to the information given including the addition, withdrawal, relocation or restructuring of courses. We also reserve the right to update our terms and conditions and privacy policy without notice.
The College is not responsible for the content or actions of external Internet sites. The College also cannot take any responsibility for any translations made by any translation tool used to convert the website's contents. Additionally for any content we create in any language other than English we cannot guarantee complete accuracy in the translation.
Statistical Data Collection
We monitor and record extensively connections to and from college servers. We do this for security and in order to detect and prevent abuse as well as for statistical and performance measurement purposes. The monitoring data we collect includes browser type, domain names, traffic volumes, temporal data, IP information, and data posted from web-forms on our website.
By using this website you accept that anonymous data will be collected about how you use the website, for example what pages have visited and for how long. Also when you click a link that takes you away from the website it will tell us what site you visited. In all cases this data is totally anonymous and cannot be traced to you in any way. Data collected is only used to help us understand how the website is used so that we can for example improve how our website works.
If you wish to stop this happening you can disable the use of cookies within your web browser settings (either for all websites or just this website). The data is collected by a third party provider (Google Analytics) and for that reason we cannot place any restrictions on how data is collected or how they collect or manage it. However the information is kept safe, secure and anonymous and is only available to The College and will only be viewed by The College and approved associates where required.
Use of cookies
We use "cookies" on some parts of our site to improve the quality of the service we offer, especially to enable users with visual impairment to alter the appearance of our site to meet their needs.
What are Cookies?
Cookies are small electronic files which a website can transfer to a user's hard drive to identify a user and personalise their use of that website. Our web server automatically collects standard information such as a user's IP address, browser type, operating system, access times, etc. We also use cookies to offer ways to customise your user experience should you wish such as accessibility tools like text size increasing and decreasing.
Google Analytics Cookies
Harlow College uses Google Analytics software which places cookies on a user's device to provide us with aggregated usage data of the Harlow College website.
Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions. The cookies are used to store information, such as what time the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before, and what site referred the visitor to the web page. These cookies do not collect information that identifies a visitor. Browsers do not share first-party cookies across domains.
Analytical cookies allow us to count the number of visitors to our website, and to see how users move around the site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the quality of the delivery of our web materials. No personal information is collected or retained by means of the cookies used to generate this statistical information.
Information on the cookies used by the default configuration and use of Google Analytics is available here: https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies
How to Control How Others use Cookies on your Computer
The cookies for Google Analytics are created automatically unless the user’s browser is set to refuse them. Users can set their browsers to accept or reject all, or certain, cookies. All recent versions of popular browsers give users a level of control over cookies. Further detail on how to control how webservers use cookies on your computer (including Google Analytics cookies) is available on the www.aboutcookies.org website, which contains a guide to deleting and controlling cookies.
Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on
As a user you can prevent Google Analytics collecting traffic log data. To provide website visitors with more choice on how their data is collected Google Analytics has developed the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js) to indicate that information about the website visit should not be sent to Google Analytics.
If you want to opt out, download and install the add-on for your current web browser, it is available from http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and enables a user to opt out. The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on is available for Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Opera.
Get the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on
Get in Touch
Find UsCourse EnquiriesHow Are We Doing?Terms & ConditionsStay in TouchSupport Services
HomeWelcomeLoginSmart SearchStudy OptionsHNC & HNDA LevelsT LevelsVocational CoursesApprenticeshipsHigher EducationAccess to HEPart-time & Adult CoursesEnglish, Maths & ESOLBright FuturesSupported StudiesOnline and On Campuse-LearningLeadership and ManagementStansted Airport CollegeEmployersHAMECChoose UsCareers AdviceHere to HelpBe an AmbassadorStudent LifeWe Win AwardsMake a DifferenceFor EmployersApplyOnline Applicant HubEnrolment FAQsFull-time CoursesPart-time CoursesApprenticeshipse-Learning CoursesLearner LoansCountdown to CollegeYour CommitmentOpen EventsFull-time Guide 2021/22Stansted Airport College Guide 21-22Study Levels ExplainedAboutReturn to College FAQsTerm Dates 2020/21COVID-19 AdviceNews & EventsGovernanceJob VacanciesUpcoming EventsSafeguardingPoliciesEquality & DiversitySixth FormSkylight RestaurantHAMECTravel InfoDigital SupportData ProtectionFinancialsApple Distinguished SchoolBritish Values at Harlow CollegeNew Student InfoContactFind UsCourse EnquiriesHow Are We Doing?Terms & ConditionsStay in TouchSupport Services
